<!-- this questions file works for a single HIT  -->
<!-- HITID = 36FQTHX306J8YJTE8HJB39L2B1GB30 (Use to Get Results)-->
<HTMLQuestion xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2011-11-11/HTMLQuestion.xsd">
<HTMLContent><![CDATA[
<!-- YOUR HTML BEGINS -->
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html; charset=UTF-8'/>
<script type='text/javascript' src='https://s3.amazonaws.com/mturk-public/externalHIT_v1.js'></script>
</head>
<body>
<form name='mturk_form' method='post' id='mturk_form' action='https://www.mturk.com/mturk/externalSubmit'><input type='hidden' value='' name='assignmentId' id='assignmentId'/>
<h2>Fake Review Detection</h2>
<h3> Review: "I had 2 days of medical appointments during a heat wave.  Air conditioning was thankfully robust and our room was quite clean.  Parking and food is close by, along with a drugstore.  Food offerings won’t make the Michelin guide , but are adequate.  And if you don’t mind a good walk, Fenway Park is just down Brookline Ave.  Just head for the iconic and comforting Citgo sign.    Also , a quick shout out to Angel, the highly efficient front office mgr. who will go the extra mile to make sure your visit is pleasant!"</h3>
<div class="panel-body">
<input type="radio" name="question_1" value="False"> Fake<br>
<input type="radio" name="question_1" value="True"> Real<br>
</div>
<h3> Review: "We were here for parents weekend and although the hotel was busy, they checked us in quickly, allowing us to unwind before we met our party. The room is smallish, but comfy and the water is HOT! Location is amazing - can walk to pretty much everything  and very close to the train station... we'll definitely come back again..."</h3>
<div>
<div class="panel-body">
<input type="radio" name="question_2" value="False"> Fake<br>
<input type="radio" name="question_2" value="True"> Real<br>
</div>
<h3> Review: "I would stay in this hotel if I have very few options or limited option of hotels in Boston. Some of their services are good while some are worst. Lke food is good but rooms are messy. I'd suggest to have a look at hotel room physically before booking"</h3>
<div>
<div class="panel-body">
<input type="radio" name="question_3" value="False"> Fake<br>
<input type="radio" name="question_3" value="True"> Real<br>
</div>
<h3> Review: "Was just baffled when I checked in the intercontinental hotel. Lovely room as usual. The issue is that they give you no water in the room to drink and a locked fridge.   So I go to the front desk and ask about water. I am handed an 8 ounce bottle of drinking water. I asked for another and the agent reluctantly handed me two more. I asked could I buy a large bottle of premium water for coffee in the room, and the answer was the ‚Äúmanager is not here right now and he has the key. I find it strange that a four-star hotel forgets about drinking water in a room for guests paying a premium price. To consider in this age that you would use Covid as an excuse to strip your rooms of the small comforts is inexcusable. "</h3>
<div class="panel-body">
<input type="radio" name="question_4" value="False"> Fake<br>
<input type="radio" name="question_4" value="True"> Real<br>
</div>
<p><input type='submit' id='submitButton' value='Submit' /></p></form>
<script language='Javascript'>turkSetAssignmentID();</script>
</body></html>
<!-- YOUR HTML ENDS -->
]]>
</HTMLContent>
<FrameHeight>600</FrameHeight>
</HTMLQuestion>
